Alright, in this lesson, we'll talk about
how we can convert this type of audio
where to get it, you know
MP3, right
I usually get it from this website
we can use this site to convert the MP3 files we need
here you can choose the broadcaster
and the audio
the volume level, yeah
Alright, this place should not have any delay.
It works like this for the conversion.
There are these types of conversions.
It's about what text you want to convert.
You input it here.
Then you can proceed with the conversion and download.
This is what I usually use.
After the synthesis, the audio,
it's in MP3 format.
I've already converted so much here.
We've already converted from zero to nine here.
And there are these as well.
If this time is too short,
Like this single digit,
The duration is too brief.
You can insert something here.
That is, insert a pause here.
And a 0.5 millisecond pause.
It might just work
Otherwise, it's too short
You might encounter an error when converting the MP3 file
I've already converted it
Here, we're generating the speech synthesis into an MP3 file.
Right here
Of course, you can try it out yourselves
And this is where I've already done the um
Oh, this should be a P3 file
I should change this name.
This is a P3 file.
Let me change it.
Here, this is P3.
P3 file.
And then,
We need to put this in our source code.
Let’s move this.
Let’s change the note.
This process takes quite a bit of time.
So if you're lazy about it,
just use mine.
I'll place this here,
and this one won't be needed.
If you decide to convert it directly, it's the same as the last class.
Just convert it using the P3 tool.
Convert each file one by one.
That's how you do it.
Then after the conversion,
Once we download this,
After downloading it,
place it in the audio directory.
We can put this in the resources folder.
extract the entire package.
Let’s set it aside for now.
We’ll put it in here.
We won’t need this for the moment.
Is it possible?
Yeah, let's put it in this folder first.
Then later we'll move it to our resources folder.
Take a look.
We'll put it in here.
Create a resource directory.
Go ahead and create it.
Under the main directory.
Then we'll create a new folder.
Resource
Then we'll place this in our file.
We'll drag all the P3 files over here.
These are binary files.
Place them here.
These are the ones we'll be using.
First, from 0 to 19,
these are numbers.
which can be combined in any way.
When it comes to playback
you can mix and match freely
since we're talking about Bluetooth
actually, connecting to Bluetooth
our Bluetooth name shouldn't be fixed
we can generate a random number later
the prefix can be whatever we want
and the suffix can be random digits
then you can broadcast the notification
The name to connect to the Bluetooth is
What does the name look like, right?
It should be a random number, so
Otherwise, if you have multiple devices together with the same name,
It would definitely be chaotic.
Here, um, in this case,
We have a voice prompt for entering the Bluetooth settings,
I wrote it like this,
Anyway, this is our button
So, if we use the button to wake it up
Because in the early stages, we might use the button to wake it up
You're working on speech recognition, right?
Then, this is when we enter into
The system successfully starts up, and there’s a notification sound
And this is the notification sound for when the WiFi configuration is complete
The sound indicating successful configuration is also here
Then this is the entire audio file, the P3 file
Placed here
We’ll cover it in the next class
How we play this file
We’ll discuss that in the next class
That’s all for this part